# Carly La

carlyla@uw.edu 425.563.4500 Seattle, WA

Experienced in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript based programming with a background in Public Health. Enthusiastic, self-motivated, goal-driven professional who possesses excellent communication skills and work ethic. Passionate about enriching our communities and solving problems through technology and programming!

## **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

#### NF Personalized Health

- Currently developing a personalized symptom tracking application for patients with Neurofibromatosis
- Aiming to increase easier communication between providers and patients, provide a platform for consistent monitorization of unusual changes or cafe-au-lait spots over time, and support NF genotype-phenotype research
- Submitting to Children's Tumor Foundation's Neurofibromatosis Hackathon
- <u>Utilizing</u>: Ruby on Rails, JavaScript. React, Reactstrap, PostgreSQL

## Simplize Project Managing App

- Developed a project managing application all-inclusive with idea bulletin boards, task boards, and issue tracking great for remote collaboration and providing an environment for accountability and efficiency
- Integrated React Beautiful DND to create interactive drag-n-drop features for greater user flexibility
- <u>Utilized</u>: Ruby on Rails, JavaScript. React, Redux, Reactstrap, Material UI, PostgreSQL

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Frontend Engineer October 2020 – Present

Free Uk Genealogy

Seattle, WA

- Redeveloping the core website with JavaScript, HTML/CSS to improve user experience, be mobile-friendly, and provide easier navigation to subsidiary organizations
- Building HTML/CSS theme to standardize web design across all pages based on brand guidelines

Operations Coordinator January 2019 – June 2020

Paul Gauguin Cruises

Bellevue, WA

- Directed the coordination of air, hotels, and transportation for 10,000+ guests
- Conducted 300 quality reviews to ensure every reservation was complete for a fluid travel experience
- Managed communication with over a dozen hotel and airlines partners, and monitored hotel/air block space inventory
- Lead new employee trainings and provided support through mentoring, observation and feedback
- Utilized Resco and Amadeus Reservation System

## Student IT Consultant July 2014 – August 2015

University of Washington Information Technology

Seattle, WA

- Provided university systems assistance for over 50,000 students, 30,000 faculty, staff and clinicians as well as visitors.
- Experienced in providing general IT customer support, and assistance with mailing listservs and UW accounts.

## **EDUCATION**

Flatiron School September, 2020

Software Engineering Seattle, WA

550+ clocked hours learning and implementing Ruby, Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, React, Redux, MySQL, Git

### University of Washington

June, 2017

Seattle, WA

Bachelor of Science, Public Health

- Nutritional Sciences Minor
- Honors: 3.72 GPA, Annual Dean's List High-Scholarship Award, Lyle F. and Ruth Wilson Scholarship
- UW Student Public Health Association, Chinese Student Association, Huskies for Kids